[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "And that's all someone would need to do to fire a shot, if it was fully loaded?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "all", "someone", "would", "need", "to", "do", "to", "fire", "a", "shot", ",", "if", "it", "was", "fully", "loaded", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Do you know whose blood that was?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "whose", "blood", "that", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP$", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "I just got a partial DNA profile and that matched Trayvon Martin.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "got", "a", "partial", "DNA", "profile", "and", "that", "matched", "Trayvon", "Martin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "The DNA you developed from the pistol grip of the defendant's gun, it was positive for blood, correct?", "question_tokens": ["The", "DNA", "you", "developed", "from", "the", "pistol", "grip", "of", "the", "defendant", "'s", "gun", ",", "it", "was", "positive", "for", "blood", ",", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "And then there was a mixture, the major matched the defendant, George Zimmerman?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "there", "was", "a", "mixture", ",", "the", "major", "matched", "the", "defendant", ",", "George", "Zimmerman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "And you were able to exclude Trayvon Martin as having DNA on the pistol grip, is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "were", "able", "to", "exclude", "Trayvon", "Martin", "as", "having", "DNA", "on", "the", "pistol", "grip", ",", "is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Yes, Trayvon Martin was excluded as being a possible contributor to this mixture on the grip.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Trayvon", "Martin", "was", "excluded", "as", "being", "a", "possible", "contributor", "to", "this", "mixture", "on", "the", "grip", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RBS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Where are we left then in terms of George Zimmerman's claim that his life was at risk?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "we", "left", "then", "in", "terms", "of", "George", "Zimmerman", "'s", "claim", "that", "his", "life", "was", "at", "risk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yes, well, you know, we should point out, of course, that the jury here, most of them came in with a very limited knowledge of this case.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "should", "point", "out", ",", "of", "course", ",", "that", "the", "jury", "here", ",", "most", "of", "them", "came", "in", "with", "a", "very", "limited", "knowledge", "of", "this", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "They're going into a weekend, 48 hours for that jury to think about it before the defense really get a chance to come back?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "going", "into", "a", "weekend", ",", "48", "hours", "for", "that", "jury", "to", "think", "about", "it", "before", "the", "defense", "really", "get", "a", "chance", "to", "come", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Is that the case?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, you know, there has to be a voice identification of that screams.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "has", "to", "be", "a", "voice", "identification", "of", "that", "screams", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "How do you feel as you approach the end of the prosecution?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "as", "you", "approach", "the", "end", "of", "the", "prosecution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "I disagree with that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "disagree", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "How significant was that moment in court do you think today?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", "was", "that", "moment", "in", "court", "do", "you", "think", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I think it's very significant because we also heard evidence there was no George Zimmerman DNA on Trayvon's hands or under his fingernails or on the cuffs of his sleeve.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "significant", "because", "we", "also", "heard", "evidence", "there", "was", "no", "George", "Zimmerman", "DNA", "on", "Trayvon", "'s", "hands", "or", "under", "his", "fingernails", "or", "on", "the", "cuffs", "of", "his", "sleeve", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Good", "Rachel Jeantel", "George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Is there any merit to that argument?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "merit", "to", "that", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I think there is no merit to that because we've heard all these theories that the star witness of this case would be Jon Good or Rachel Jeantel, when all along George Zimmerman has given at least five statements.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "is", "no", "merit", "to", "that", "because", "we", "'ve", "heard", "all", "these", "theories", "that", "the", "star", "witness", "of", "this", "case", "would", "be", "Jon", "Good", "or", "Rachel", "Jeantel", ",", "when", "all", "along", "George", "Zimmerman", "has", "given", "at", "least", "five", "statements", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "What is the answer to that question, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "answer", "to", "that", "question", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, let me give you the background.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "give", "you", "the", "background", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do you consider yourself a fair person?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "consider", "yourself", "a", "fair", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Would that be true?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "be", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "That would be true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Well, let me ask you something, while we're talking here, you're a professional but most people who would not be a professional, if I'm asking you questions that are on television, would you think you'd be a little bit nervous?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "ask", "you", "something", ",", "while", "we", "'re", "talking", "here", ",", "you", "'re", "a", "professional", "but", "most", "people", "who", "would", "not", "be", "a", "professional", ",", "if", "I", "'m", "asking", "you", "questions", "that", "are", "on", "television", ",", "would", "you", "think", "you", "'d", "be", "a", "little", "bit", "nervous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJS", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "I mean, I wouldn't be, but I understand that having interviewed many, many people that most people are quite nervous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "be", ",", "but", "I", "understand", "that", "having", "interviewed", "many", ",", "many", "people", "that", "most", "people", "are", "quite", "nervous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "And as quite nervous, do you think people interpret somebody's being nervous as perhaps not being truthful?", "question_tokens": ["And", "as", "quite", "nervous", ",", "do", "you", "think", "people", "interpret", "somebody", "'s", "being", "nervous", "as", "perhaps", "not", "being", "truthful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Or being overly defensive.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "being", "overly", "defensive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "And for that reason, there is nothing to gain by putting Zimmerman on the stand given we already have five different effective statements from him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "for", "that", "reason", ",", "there", "is", "nothing", "to", "gain", "by", "putting", "Zimmerman", "on", "the", "stand", "given", "we", "already", "have", "five", "different", "effective", "statements", "from", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "So I would first make sure that every one of the jurors understood that the decision to take the stand is going to be my decision, and the reasons why I wouldn't have somebody take the stand, just being nervous, perhaps that alone would make you think maybe he's not being truthful.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "I", "would", "first", "make", "sure", "that", "every", "one", "of", "the", "jurors", "understood", "that", "the", "decision", "to", "take", "the", "stand", "is", "going", "to", "be", "my", "decision", ",", "and", "the", "reasons", "why", "I", "would", "n't", "have", "somebody", "take", "the", "stand", ",", "just", "being", "nervous", ",", "perhaps", "that", "alone", "would", "make", "you", "think", "maybe", "he", "'s", "not", "being", "truthful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Is there anything to be gained, Robert, by Zimmerman taking the stand given the amount of material from his own mouth that we've already heard?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "to", "be", "gained", ",", "Robert", ",", "by", "Zimmerman", "taking", "the", "stand", "given", "the", "amount", "of", "material", "from", "his", "own", "mouth", "that", "we", "'ve", "already", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert", "Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "What is that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "The jury can see him, look him in the eye, and that's the best way to make a determination if you're believing that person was actually in fear for his life.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "jury", "can", "see", "him", ",", "look", "him", "in", "the", "eye", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "the", "best", "way", "to", "make", "a", "determination", "if", "you", "'re", "believing", "that", "person", "was", "actually", "in", "fear", "for", "his", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Could that be a tipping point for them to say, we've got to have George up there?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "that", "be", "a", "tipping", "point", "for", "them", "to", "say", ",", "we", "'ve", "got", "to", "have", "George", "up", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "HAPIRO: You know, it is so hard to evaluate.", "answer_tokens": ["HAPIRO", ":", "You", "know", ",", "it", "is", "so", "hard", "to", "evaluate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Right, because you can't win a cross-examination of a grieving mother, right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "because", "you", "ca", "n't", "win", "a", "cross-examination", "of", "a", "grieving", "mother", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Or of any relative of a victim.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "of", "any", "relative", "of", "a", "victim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Well, have they overcharged to start with?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "have", "they", "overcharged", "to", "start", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I think they have overcharged.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "have", "overcharged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Isn't that intent there to think badly of this person?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "intent", "there", "to", "think", "badly", "of", "this", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "EX", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, malice is a legal term.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "malice", "is", "a", "legal", "term", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Isn't that ill will?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "ill", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I think it possibly could be interpreted by people as ill will, but it -- again, you have the reasonable doubt standard that you have to get over.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "possibly", "could", "be", "interpreted", "by", "people", "as", "ill", "will", ",", "but", "it", "--", "again", ",", "you", "have", "the", "reasonable", "doubt", "standard", "that", "you", "have", "to", "get", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "That is what with racial profiling or just profiling of this is a bad person, he's still coming at him with malicious intent, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "what", "with", "racial", "profiling", "or", "just", "profiling", "of", "this", "is", "a", "bad", "person", ",", "he", "'s", "still", "coming", "at", "him", "with", "malicious", "intent", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I don't know but that's going to be the question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "but", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "the", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Is that a key question?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "key", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "That is a key question and that's what the lawyers are going to be arguing in their closing argument and that's what the jury is going to be sitting on and deciding.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "a", "key", "question", "and", "that", "'s", "what", "the", "lawyers", "are", "going", "to", "be", "arguing", "in", "their", "closing", "argument", "and", "that", "'s", "what", "the", "jury", "is", "going", "to", "be", "sitting", "on", "and", "deciding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you believe him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I haven't heard him testify directly --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "heard", "him", "testify", "directly", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "From what you've seen in the statements and the interviews?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "'ve", "seen", "in", "the", "statements", "and", "the", "interviews", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Simpson", "Simpson"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Do you feel that it's as a motive, as, say, the O.J. Simpson case?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "it", "'s", "as", "a", "motive", ",", "as", ",", "say", ",", "the", "O.J.", "Simpson", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "You know, I don't want to compare anything to the Simpson case and I don't really talk about the Simpson case.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "compare", "anything", "to", "the", "Simpson", "case", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "talk", "about", "the", "Simpson", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["O.J. Simpson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oscar Pistorius"], "LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Is it just not an excuse for almost every gang banger thug in America to say hey, I was just acting in self-defense?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "just", "not", "an", "excuse", "for", "almost", "every", "gang", "banger", "thug", "in", "America", "to", "say", "hey", ",", "I", "was", "just", "acting", "in", "self-defense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "You know, we're going to see the opposite side of that in the Oscar Pistorius case where in South Africa you cannot use deadly force unless deadly force is being used upon you.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "see", "the", "opposite", "side", "of", "that", "in", "the", "Oscar", "Pistorius", "case", "where", "in", "South", "Africa", "you", "can", "not", "use", "deadly", "force", "unless", "deadly", "force", "is", "being", "used", "upon", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "How significant could that be in tipping the scales back in the favor of the prosecution case?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", "could", "that", "be", "in", "tipping", "the", "scales", "back", "in", "the", "favor", "of", "the", "prosecution", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "I think it can be significant in the sense that it's going to be very emotional testimony.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "can", "be", "significant", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "very", "emotional", "testimony", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "So it really is all or nothing for George Zimmerman, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "really", "is", "all", "or", "nothing", "for", "George", "Zimmerman", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "If it is enhanced the way I think it will be, they could win the battle and lose the war, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "it", "is", "enhanced", "the", "way", "I", "think", "it", "will", "be", ",", "they", "could", "win", "the", "battle", "and", "lose", "the", "war", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Would you put him on the stand, particularly if the Trayvon family members' testimony is heart rendering and you sense the jury had been moved by him?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "put", "him", "on", "the", "stand", ",", "particularly", "if", "the", "Trayvon", "family", "members", "'", "testimony", "is", "heart", "rendering", "and", "you", "sense", "the", "jury", "had", "been", "moved", "by", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Honestly, Piers, I just don't see any percentage in that.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "see", "any", "percentage", "in", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "What do you think that will be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "that", "will", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "If I was looking at it from a pure legal standpoint, I would say an acquittal.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "was", "looking", "at", "it", "from", "a", "pure", "legal", "standpoint", ",", "I", "would", "say", "an", "acquittal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "You don't have to wait until you are almost dead before you can defend yourself?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "wait", "until", "you", "are", "almost", "dead", "before", "you", "can", "defend", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Doesn't there have to be accountability for that?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "there", "have", "to", "be", "accountability", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Not necessarily in the criminal justice system.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "necessarily", "in", "the", "criminal", "justice", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "There has to be some form of justice for Trayvon Martin, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "has", "to", "be", "some", "form", "of", "justice", "for", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "That is a different ball game, just as even in a civil action, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "a", "different", "ball", "game", ",", "just", "as", "even", "in", "a", "civil", "action", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mohamed Morsy", "Mohamed Morsy"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBN", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Who is in charge?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "in", "charge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "They are very much the strongest institution in the country and they laid down the law 48 hours ago to Mohamed Morsy and the opposition saying, that if you don't get your act together, you're out and we're in, and what happened was last night we heard a speech from Mohamed Morsy who, as he made it clear, that he wasn't going to give in to their ultimatum.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "very", "much", "the", "strongest", "institution", "in", "the", "country", "and", "they", "laid", "down", "the", "law", "48", "hours", "ago", "to", "Mohamed", "Morsy", "and", "the", "opposition", "saying", ",", "that", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "get", "your", "act", "together", ",", "you", "'re", "out", "and", "we", "'re", "in", ",", "and", "what", "happened", "was", "last", "night", "we", "heard", "a", "speech", "from", "Mohamed", "Morsy", "who", ",", "as", "he", "made", "it", "clear", ",", "that", "he", "was", "n't", "going", "to", "give", "in", "to", "their", "ultimatum", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "But where does it leave democracy in Egypt, the democracy that everyone celebrated with the Arab spring now looks to be in taters?", "question_tokens": ["But", "where", "does", "it", "leave", "democracy", "in", "Egypt", ",", "the", "democracy", "that", "everyone", "celebrated", "with", "the", "Arab", "spring", "now", "looks", "to", "be", "in", "taters", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["spring"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Samantha, how bad is it going to be?", "question_tokens": ["Samantha", ",", "how", "bad", "is", "it", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "It's already been pretty bad today across much of the Deep South, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "already", "been", "pretty", "bad", "today", "across", "much", "of", "the", "Deep", "South", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]